{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "anime": "One Piece",
      "question": "Who is the main character in One Piece?",
      "correct_answer": "Luffy",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sanji", "Robin", "Zoro"]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "anime": "One Piece",
      "question": "Who wants to be the world strongest swords man?",
      "correct_answer": "Zoro",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Brook", "Oden", "Shanks"]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "anime": "One Piece",
      "question": "Who is the main character in One Piece?",
      "correct_answer": "Luffy",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Sanji", "Robin", "Zoro"]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "anime": "One Piece",
      "question": "Who resigned from the position of Warlord?",
      "correct_answer": "Doflamingo",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jimbei", "Moriah", "Jimbei"]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "anime": "Naruto",
      "question": "Who is not a Jonin?",
      "correct_answer": "Iruka",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Might Guy", "Asuma", "Kakashi"]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": " A wounded Z fighter would restore the full health by using which item?",
      "correct_answer": "Senzu Bean",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Capsule Medicine", "Saiyan Liquid", "Potara"]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": "How did Goku reach the planet of King Kai first time?",
      "correct_answer": "Walk along the Snake Way",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Korin Tower",
        "Teleport instantly",
        "Call the Dragon God to make a wish"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": "What is the name of Goku's father?",
      "correct_answer": "Bardock",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Goten", "Cabba", "Turles"]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": "One minute in the in the real world is equivalent to how much time in the  Hyperbolic Time Chamber?",
      "correct_answer": "6 Hours",
      "incorrect_answers": ["1 Day", "1 Year", "600 minutes"]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": "What is the highest level of Super Saiyan that Vegeta can reach?",
      "correct_answer": "Level 2",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Level 1", "Level 3", "Level 4"]
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": "Which wearable device is used by the Friezaâ€™s army to measure power levels?",
      "correct_answer": "Scouter",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Gourd of Mist", "Radar", "Power Pole"]
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": "Which race does Piccolo belong to?",
      "correct_answer": "Namekian",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Human", "Hybrid", "Saiyan"]
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": "Goku learnt his Instant Transmission skill in which planet?",
      "correct_answer": "Planet Yardrat",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Planet Kaishin", "Planet Namek", "Planet Earth"]
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "anime": "Dragon Ball Z",
      "question": "What is the name of Goku's wife?",
      "correct_answer": "Chi Chi",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Hinata", "Hancock", "Launch"]
    }
  ]
}
